https://tedthorsen.com/privacy-policy

Menu Product CategoriesTed's Hot DealsBulk ContainersIndustrial Bulk ContainersCollapsible Bulk ContainersHarvest Bulk ContainersIntermediate Bulk Containers - Liquid IBCLids & Accessories for Bulk ContainersPlastic PalletsPlastic Rackable PalletsPlastic Economy Export PalletsDistribution & Storage ContainersAttached Lid Distribution ContainersSecurity SealsStorage TubsPlastic Tubs & TrunksStackable Totes & TraysFoldable CratesIndustrial Laundry CartsCanvas Laundry Baskets & TrucksVinyl Laundry Baskets & TrucksPlastic Linen Trucks
Account
Privacy Policy
We at Ted Thorsen appreciate the trust you place in us and in our website: TedThorsen.com. We are committed to our customers, and we strive to protect the privacy and security of your personal information. Our privacy policy describes the information we collect, how we use it, and the security measures taken to assure your information is protected.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Upon visiting our site, our server collects basic information such as: statistical information about which web pages you viewed, any referring sites which may have led you to our site, IP addresses, domain names, etc.
This basic information is used internally for testing, marketing, and evaluation of our site. No personally identifiable data is recorded for these purposes.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
During a webstore transaction on our site, we collect your personal information for sales, marketing, purchasing, and billing purposes only. We do not share your personal information with any outside sources.
INFORMATION SHARING POLICY
We do not share your information with any other parties for marketing or advertising purposes. We do, however, share your information — when necessary — with our vendors and manufacturers, using the strictest confidentiality guidelines. In these cases, the information shared is only that which will assist us in the ordinary course of order fulfillment, shipping, and billing.
E-MAIL
As a valued customer, you may occasionally receive promotional e-mails, or catalogs via postal mail. If you do not wish to receive e-mails from us, please send an e-mail, with the e-mail address you wish to be removed, to: info@tedthorsen.com, and we will gladly remove you from our e-mail list.
COOKIES
To better serve you, we may store cookies to speed the operation of our log-in and shipping cart functions. A cookie is merely a small text file and does not contain sensitive information such as credit card numbers or sensitive billing information. Cookies enable us to recognize returning customers and to help simplify the online shopping experience.
SECURITY
Ted Thorsen is committed to providing you with a secure online shopping experience. We have many security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information we collect. We use 128-bit encryption technology and Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) in all areas where your personal information is required. You can validate the security of our website by clicking the security button in your brower (usually, within the URL toolbar.)
